bettermarks.com 2003-06-24

# WRC (UK) - Privacy Policy

**WRC (UK) Privacy Policy**

**Our Commitment:**  
WRC (UK) respects your privacy and only collects the minimum information necessary for the delivery of our services to our customers and keeps all information confidential and secured. WRC (UK) may periodically send email to our customers informing them of updates to our services. WRC (UK) does not share any information (including email addresses) with third parties except as detailed below.

**Security:  
**Our site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Certain areas of our site use industry standard SSL to encrypt sensitive data, such as credit card numbers. We record ip address of persons submitting order forms to aid fraud prevention and will disclose any information necessary to fully co-operate with law enforcement authorities in investigating suspected lawbreakers.

**Order Forms:  
**Our site uses forms for customers to request information, and to order products, and services. We collect Contact information (e.g. name, address, company name, URL, and email address) and Financial information (e.g. account or credit card numbers). Information from order forms is used to generate customer accounts. The customer's Contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Financial information is used to bill the customer for products and services supplied.

**Cookies:  
**A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. WRC (UK) utilises cookies in our advert tracking system to ensure even rotation of advertisements. Our cookies are in no way linked to any personally identifiable information gathered while on our site. Some of our advertisers may also utilise cookies, but the use of these is governed by their own privacy policy, not this one.

**Sharing of Information:  
**Information collected during order processing, delivery, installation, support and maintenance of our Services may for the purposes of providing our Services be processed by WRC (UK), its provisioning entities, affiliates and agents both within and outside the European Economic Area, and outside the country or countries where the data is collected. Specifically:

  * For the purposes of opening an individual Domain Account and registering domain names, Contact and Financial information is submitted to Dotster, Inc ([http://www.dotster.com](http://www.qksrv.net/click-1061526-514796)), a top ten ICANN-accredited domain registrar.
  * For the purposes of administering domain names, Contact information is submitted to Network Solutions, Inc. ([http://www.netsol.com](http://www.netsol.com/)) or one of our other ICANN-accredited domain registrars.
  * For the purposes of processing credit card transactions for Web Hosting orders, Contact information and Financial information is shared with Card Service International ([http://www.cardservice.com](http://www.cardservice.com/)) and American Express International ([http://www.americanexpress.com](http://www.americanexpress.com/)) as appropriate.
  * For the purposes of search engine submission, Contact information including web site URL must be sent to the Search Engines listed on the Search Engine Submission Page.

**Links:**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that WRC (UK) is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy:  
**WRC (UK) may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
